http://www.waldorfschool.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
WSOC values and respects your privacy. This policy governs its Web site data collection via www.waldorfschool.com. By using the WSOC Web site, you are deemed to have consented to the practices described in this policy.
Collection of Personal Information
WSOC shall keep confidential personal information that it collects such as first and last name, electronic mail address, home or other physical address, telephone number, and fax number.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by WSOC. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by WSOC for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the WSOC Web site.
Use of Personal Information
WSOC will inform you of the purpose for its collection of information. It does not intend to transfer or otherwise share your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described below. If you choose to provide us with your personal information, the information will be stored on a secure server and we will use that information at WSOC or we may transfer it third party service provider as necessary. WSOC will not record your credit card number.
WSOC may also collect electronic information during your use of its Web site. WSOC may collect domain information to enable it to analyze how visitors use this site. This data enables WSOC to become more familiar with people who visit its site including how often they visit, their access times, and browser type. WSOC will use this information to improve its services and obtain statistics regarding the use of its site.
WSOC may also use the information to which it has access to provide you with or solicit other information and to let you know of additional services that may be of interest to you.
Do Not Track Notice
WSOC does not track its visitors over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. However, some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. If you are visiting such sites, Safari allows you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked. If you would like to learn how to set Safari so that websites do not track you, go here: http://support.apple.com/kb/PH11952.
Use of Cookies
Some pages on this site may use “cookies” — small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. Cookies cannot read information from your hard drive. They will also not run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID to track the pages visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. These files are used for site registration and to customize your visit to the site. The cookie will tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page on the Web site, and it will customize the site’s features for you.
Your Web browser may notify you when you are receiving a cookie and it may give you the choice to accept or reject it. You can set your browser to warn you about cookies, and to determine if you want to refuse all cookies. If you chose not to accept cookies, some pages may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on this site.
Information Sharing
WSOC does not share your information without your permission, except if you consent to share your information to a third party service provider working on WSOC’s behalf.
WSOC will also disclose your personal information, if required to do so by law, or in urgent circumstances, such as, but not limited to, those that involve the need to protect an individual’s personal safety, the protection of the public or the protection of WSOC’s rights or property. WSOC will not trade, sell, rent, lease, or otherwise share your information to anyone, or let anyone use it except if you have authorized its use.
Protecting the Privacy of Children
Children under 13 years old are not the target audience for our Web site. To protect their privacy, WSOC prohibits the solicitation of personal information from these children.
Internet Security
WSOC strives to protect your personal information; however, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Please take proactive steps to secure your personal data, such as frequently changing your passwords.
Links to Third Party Sites
WSOC’s Web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. WSOC encourages you to learn about the privacy practices and policies of those companies.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
WSOC reserves the right to change, modify or update this policy at any time without notice. Any substantial changes in the way WSOC uses your personal information will be posted on this site.
Contact Information
WSOC welcomes your comments regarding its privacy policy. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 949-574-7775.
Subscribe To Our NewsletterLet's keep in touch
SUBSCRIBE!
You have Successfully Subscribed!
X
WE ARE OPEN FOR ON-CAMPUS LEARNING
